// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which one of the following is an application of Stack Data Structure?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Managing function calls",
      "The stock span problem",
      "Arithmetic expression evaluation",
      "All of the above"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Process of inserting an element in stack is called ____________.",
    answer: "Push",
    options: [
      "Create",
      "Push",
      "Evaluation",
      "Pop"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In a stack, if a user tries to remove an element from empty stack it is called _________.",
    answer: "Underflow",
    options: [
      "Underflow",
      "Empty collection",
      "Overflow",
      "Garbage Collection"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Entries in a stack are . What is the meaning of this statement?",
    answer: "There is a Sequential entry that is one by one",
    options: [
      "A collection of stacks is sortable",
      "Stack entries may be compared with the '<' operation",
      "The entries are stored in a linked list",
      "There is a Sequential entry that is one by one"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The prefix form of A-B/ (C * D ⋀ E) is?",
    answer: "-A/B*C⋀DE",
    options: [
      "-/*⋀ACBDE",
      "ABCD*⋀DE",
      "-A/B*C⋀DE",
      "-A/BC*⋀DE"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + – *:",
    answer: "Something between 15 and 100",
    options: [
      "Something between -5 and -15",
      "Something between 5 and -5",
      "Something between 5 and 15",
      "Something between 15 and 100"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following applications may use a stack?",
    answer: "All of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "A parentheses balancing program",
      "Tracking of local variables at run time",
      "Compiler Syntax Analyzer",
      "All of the mentioned"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The postfix form of A*B+C/D is?",
    answer: "A*BC+/D",
    options: [
      "*AB/CD+",
      "AB*CD/+",
      "A*BC+/D",
      "ABCD+/*"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Process of removing an element from stack is called __________",
    answer: "Pod",
    options: [
      "Create",
      "Push",
      "Evaluation",
      "Pod"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Consider the usual algorithm for determining whether a sequence of parentheses is balanced.The maximum number of parentheses that appear on the stack AT ANY ONE TIME when the algorithm analyzes: (()(())(())) are:",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4 or more"

    ]
  },


];